export default [
  {
    difficulty: 5,
    points: 100000,
    question: 'In 1768, Captain James Cook set out to explore which ocean?',
    correctAnswer: 'Pacific Ocean',
    answers: ['Atlantic Ocean', 'Indian Ocean', 'Pacific Ocean', 'Arctic Ocean']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 5,
    points: 100000,
    question:
      'The phrase: ”I think, therefore I am” was coined by which philosopher?',
    correctAnswer: 'Descartes',
    answers: ['Socrates', 'Plato', 'Aristotle', 'Descartes']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 5,
    points: 100000,
    question: 'Which two months are named after Emperors of the Roman Empire?',
    correctAnswer: 'July and August',
    answers: [
      'January and February',
      'March and April',
      'May and June',
      'July and August'
    ]
  },
  {
    difficulty: 2,
    points: 5000,
    question: 'What is actually electricity?',
    correctAnswer: 'A flow of electrons',
    answers: [
      'A flow of water',
      'A flow of air',
      'A flow of electrons',
      'A flow of atoms'
    ]
  },
  {
    difficulty: 2,
    points: 5000,
    question: 'Goulash is a type of beef soup in which country?',
    correctAnswer: 'Hungary',
    answers: ['Hungary', 'Czech Republic', 'Slovakia', 'Ireland']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 2,
    points: 5000,
    question: 'Which is the easiest way to tell the age of many trees?',
    correctAnswer: 'To count the rings on the trunk',
    answers: [
      'To measure the width of the tree',
      'To count the rings on the trunk',
      'To count the number of leaves',
      'To measure the height of the tree'
    ]
  },
  {
    difficulty: 1,
    points: 2000,
    question: 'Which of the following is not an international organisation?',
    correctAnswer: 'FBI',
    answers: ['FIFA', 'NATO', 'FBI', 'ASEAN']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 1,
    points: 2000,
    question: 'Which of the following disorders is the fear of being alone?',
    correctAnswer: 'Agoraphobia',
    answers: ['Agoraphobia', 'Aerophobia', 'Acrophobia', 'Arachnophobia']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 3,
    points: 10000,
    question:
      'Which of the following is a song by the German heavy metal band “Scorpions”?',
    correctAnswer: 'Wind of Change',
    answers: [
      'Stairway to Heaven',
      'Wind of Change',
      'Don’t Stop Me Now',
      'Hey Jude'
    ]
  },
  {
    difficulty: 3,
    points: 10000,
    question: 'What do we call a newly hatched butterfly?',
    correctAnswer: 'A caterpillar',
    answers: ['A moth', 'A butter', 'A caterpillar', 'A chrysalis']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 3,
    points: 10000,
    question:
      'What was the first country to use tanks in combat during World War I?',
    correctAnswer: 'Britain',
    answers: ['France', 'Japan', 'Britain', 'Germany']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 1,
    points: 50000,
    question: 'What is the speed of sound?',
    correctAnswer: '1,200 km/h',
    answers: ['120 km/h', '1,200 km/h', '400 km/h', '700 km/h']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 4,
    points: 50000,
    question: 'In total, how many novels were written by the Bronte sisters?',
    correctAnswer: '7',
    answers: ['4', '5', '6', '7']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 4,
    points: 50000,
    question: 'Which did Viking people use as money?',
    correctAnswer: 'Jewellery',
    answers: ['Rune stones', 'Jewellery', 'Seal skins', 'Wool']
  },
  {
    difficulty: 4,
    points: 50000,
    question: 'What is the main component of the sun?',
    correctAnswer: 'Gas',
    answers: ['Liquid lava', 'Gas', 'Molten iron', 'Rock']
  }
]
